coinratecap.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy | Coinratecap

This privacy policy shows how Coin Rate Cap LTD uses and protects any information that you shared with Coin Rate Cap LTD while using this website.

Coin Rate Cap LTD is ensures that your privacy is well protected. When using this site you may be asked to provide some information such as your name and email by which you can be identified and be assured that your information will be protected and used in accordance with this privacy statement.

 Coin Rate Cap LTD may change this policy from time to time by updating this page and this will be done without user's permission. You are advised to check from time to time to ensure you are it does not violate your principles.

### Information we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Name

  * Demographic information such as postcode

  * Contact information including email address

.

### What we do with the information

We use this information gathered  to understand your needs and provide you with a better service  and user experience.

  * For record keeping.

  * Occasionally,  we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.

  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products and special offers or other information which we think you may be of interest to you using the email address which you have provided.

  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.

### Security

We aim at ensuring the safety of information you provide to us. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable all the necessary technology and physical, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect online.

How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed nor in accordance by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question before use.

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal data to 3rd parties unless we've got your full permission or square measure needed by law to try to, therefore. We have a tendency to use your personal data to send you promotional data regarding third parties that we expect you'll realize fascinating if you tell us that you simply want this to happen.

You may request details of private data that we have a tendency to hold regarding you beneath the info Protection Act 1998. a tiny low fee are due . If you'd sort of a copy of the information held on you please write to info@coinratecap.com.

If you think that any data we have a tendency to square measure holding on you is wrong or incomplete, please write to or email us. we'll surely correct any data found to be incorrect.

With your consent, we have a tendency to collect data regarding the particular location of your mobile device (for example, by victimization GPS or Bluetooth). you'll revoke this consent at any time by dynamical the preferences on your device, however doing therefore might have an effect on your ability to use all of the options and practicality of our Services. You may opt out of our promotional services by foloowing instructions on your mail.

We might provide social sharing options or alternative integrated tools that allow you share content or actions you are taking on our Services with alternative media. Your use of those options permits the sharing of data together with your friends or the general public.  For further information regarding the aim and scope of information assortment and process in reference to social sharing options, please visit the privacy policies of the third parties that offer these social sharing options.

If you still use our Services once Privacy Policy changes go into effect, you consent to the revised policy.

What are Cookies?   
A cookie is a very small piece of information that a website stores to save and collect basic information. Many cookies are essential to the operation of our website, for example to allow you to make a purchase or create an account with us. Cookies on our site are also used to customise certain areas of content just for you, and to make your browsing experience more efficient and faster. 

How we use Cookies  
Cookies on our website are used for the following purposes To enable you to login to the system To enable you to system messages To improve the website's usability by saving loading time To analyse the use of our website through Analytics software such as Google Analytics. 

Information Collected  
The cookies our website doesn't collect any private data
